<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<Stories>
  <Story ID="2019012">
    <Date>11/11/2019</Date>
    <Title>Disable a user</Title>
    <Description>
      <![CDATA[The function to disable an inactive user has been added to the Virtual Chief. <br />
To disable a user, access the user management, click on "edit" on the side of a user and then click on the trash can icon at the top right.
      ]]>
    </Description>
  </Story>
  <Story ID="2019009">
    <Date>30/09/2019</Date>
    <Title>Assign task directly to operators and Personal WebGemba</Title>
    <Description>
      <![CDATA[Now it is possible to assign tasks directly to specific operators, and not only to workstations !!! <br />
The operator can manage his tasks via the <b> Personal WebGemba </b>, which is exactly the same as the WebGemba, but only contains the tasks assigned to a specific operator.
<br />
To access the <i> Personal WebGemba </i>, click on the WorkPlace menu -> Personal WebGemba. <br />
To assign tasks to operators, after planning a product in production, click on the Operator icon. <br /> <br />
Furthermore, through the Process Manager it is possible to designate the operators that will be assigned by default to a task.
      ]]>
    </Description>
  </Story>
  <Story ID="2019008">
    <Date>30/09/2019</Date>
    <Title>Delivery week</Title>
    <Description>
      <![CDATA[Virtual Chief now allows you to view the <b>delivery week</b> instead of the exact date.<br />
To activate the display of the delivery week, enter the Departments Configuration, select the desired Department. Then, from the "Andon Department" menu, activate the "Week end of production" field in the Andon Display Fields
      ]]>
    </Description>
  </Story>
  <Story id="2019/01">
    <Date>02/01/2019</Date>
    <Title>Workstation's key performance indicators</Title>
    <Description>
      <![CDATA[In the WebGemba, are shown the most valuable key performance indicators of each workstation, suc as:
      <ul>
      <li>Produced quantity</li>
      <li>Delays</li>
      <li>Lead time</li>
      </ul>
      ]]>
    </Description>
  </Story>
  <Story id="2018/17">
    <Date>31/12/2018</Date>
    <Title>Manual recording of work intervals</Title>
    <Description>
      <![CDATA[From today it is possible to manually register / modify the work intervals registered by the operators. <br />
       To access the new interface, go to Admin --> User Management <br />
       Then click on the clock icon next to the desired user.
      ]]>
    </Description>
  </Story>
  <Story id="2018/12">
    <Date>26/11/2018</Date>
    <Title>Destination URL after login</Title>
    <Description>
      <![CDATA[Implemented the function to set an automatic login URL after login.<br />
To set up your personalized login page, log in to your personal area (MyArea) and set your destination URL.
      ]]>
    </Description>
  </Story>
  <Story id="2018/15">
    <Date>17/11/2018</Date>
    <Title>Scrollable Andon</Title>
    <Description>
      <![CDATA[It is now possible to set the Continuous Scroll of the Andon, in order to display all the orders in progress and even those not yet started.
       Furthermore, the scroll speed can be set. <br />
       For the Andon Reparto, you can access the configuration of the department (Plant -> Departments) and access the "Scrolling" section. <br />
       To configure the Complete Andon, you can access from the Admin -> Complete Andon Management menu
      ]]>
    </Description>
  </Story>
  <Story id="2018/10">
    <Date>06/10/2018</Date>
    <Title>Order External ID</Title>
    <Description>
      <![CDATA[With the external order code you can maintain the link between the data of your ERP and Virtual Chief
      ]]>
    </Description>
  </Story>
  <Story id="110">
    <Date>09/11/2017</Date>
    <Title>Quality Module</Title>
    <Description>
      <![CDATA[It now available as an option the Quality Management Module, with the following functions:
      <ul>
      <li>Non compliances' management - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=niknol6ikUQ&t=336s" target="_blank">Watch the video</a></li>
      <li>Non compliances' analysis and Risk Management - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ARWdOV0fTyE&t=49s" target="_blank">Watch the video</a></li>
      <li>Improvement actions' management with 8D form, assignment of corrective actions to Team Members and Real time progress monitoring</li>
      </ul>
      ]]>
    </Description>
  </Story>
  <Story id="113">
    <Date>31/07/2017</Date>
    <Title>Automatic check-in and check-out from workstations</Title>
      <Description>
      <![CDATA[Often using the BARCODE GEMBA interface, the task of CHECK-IN and CHECK-OUT at a workstation can represent a significant burden on the activities.<br />
Now you can configure Workstations to AUTOMATICALLY make check-in and check-out when using Gemba barcode]]>
    </Description>
  </Story>
  <Story id="109">
    <Date>16/07/2017</Date>
    <Title>BugFix: user language selection</Title>
      <Description>
      <![CDATA[In the initial configuration you can now select the user's language.]]>
    </Description>
  </Story>
  <Story id="107">
    <Date>16/07/2017</Date>
    <Title>Notice of expiration of the license of use</Title>
      <Description>
      <![CDATA[Now Kaizen Indicator System informs you 1 month in advance when your license expires.<br />Remember that in case of non-renewal, the service will be automatically stopped after 15 days from the expiry date.]]>
    </Description>
  </Story>
  <Story id="0103">
    <Date>01/07/2017</Date>
    <Title>KIS Multilanguage</Title>
    <Description>
      <![CDATA[Now <i>Kaizen Indicator System</i> speaks three languages:
      <ul>
      <li>English</li>
      <li>Spanish</li>
      <li>Italian</li>
      </ul>
      System can be used by people of different countries because every user can choose the language that he prefers
      to use Kaizen Indicato System.
      ]]>
    </Description>
  </Story>
</Stories>